Ahmed Alhisan

Experienced software engineer with a passion for developing innovative programs that expedite the efficiency and effectiveness of organizational success. Well-versed in technology and writing code to create systems that are reliable and user-friendly. I have full commitment to work hard and improve my skills.

Alhisan.Swe@gmail.com

0535991010

Riyadh, Saudi arabia

github.com/AhmedAlhisan





EDUCATION

Software Engineer

King Saud University / Riyadh 03/2013 - 01/2018



WORK EXPERIENCE

Programmer Ministry of Defense

09/2020 - Present

Tasks

- System Analsis.
- Coding (Front-End / Back-End).
- Testing.
- ▶ Deployment Windows Server 2019.
- Maintenance.
- Working with Stakeholders.

Programmer - Tmheer Program Dolf Technology

Khobar

Rivadh

Riyadh

01/2019 - 06/2019 E learning customization platform.

Tasks

- ▶ Ubuntu 16.04.
- Open-Edx Customiziation.
- Python Back-End.
- Python/Diango.



Django 4 With Example Fourth Edition



Full Professional Proficiency

Arabic

Native or Bilingual Proficiency



CERTIFICATES

Web Development Python-Django - TUWAIQ ACADDEMY (01/2023 - 03/2023)

Working Deep with python / Django and DataBase With ORM.

Front end nanodgree - UDACITY (03/2023 - Present)

Deep with JavaScript / Web APIs Asynchronous/Node Express JS

Data analysis - MISK ACADDEMY

Working with Excel & Tableau.



PROJECTS.

Rent Caravans platform

Platform helping users to find caravans for rent, by showing the newst Caravans with fair price also support who want to invest by his caravans For individuals and groups.

Track Employee Courses and Mandates

Platform helping management department, to assign, courses and mandates, for employees according to employees knowledge progress, and achievements also provide statistics for all employees.

Portfolio

About me - Project - CV Download -Blog Section - replay for blog control content by Admin.



TECHNICAL SKILLS

PYTHON Django 4.1

postman test API

SQL Server

ASP.NET Bootstrap

CSS3 HTML5

PstgreSQL

GitHub

JAVAScript

API Rest

Software Development Life Cycle [SDLC]

Deployment



SOFT SKILLS

Time management.

Communication.

Problem-solving.

Teamwork.

Work Ethics.

Attention to Details.